[Never-Ending Summer]
[Episode 2]
I'm out.
Where are you?
I saw you.
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
-Mom, are you going to Guangzhou again? -Wan, go do your homework.
I thought you would stay
A few more days this time.
Mom, I want to go
To Guangzhou with you.
Wan.
If you leave, what about Grandma?
She'll be lonely all by herself,
Right?
When I come back,
I'll bring you pretty dresses
And yummy treats, okay?
Go back now.
But every time you lie to me,
You smile just like that.
Wan.
You're still young.
There's a lot you don't understand.
If I take you with me,
Neither of us will have a good life.
Wait for me at home, okay?
I will come back.
Grandma will come get you.
Go back.
Mom!
-Go back! -Mom!
Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Am I not a good girl?
Is that why Dad doesn't want me
And neither do you?
Mom, don't leave me!
Mom!
Tell me if you need anything.
I can help you.
[Guo Xiangling] [Lu Xixiao]
Dad.
I'm going to do something wrong.
Will you forgive me?
Grilled fish!
Freshly made, right here!
Come and have a taste if you want some!
Yu.
Look at your little fish.
It's about to die.
You keep your fish tank
Facing a grilled fish stall every day.
No wonder your business isn't doing well.
That's why I'm transferring it.
See?
[Store Transfer]
The smoke from his stall is messing up
My whole setup.
If you're leaving, just leave.
What's that got to do with me?
Stop blocking my space.
You're delaying my business every day.
I don't even want to mention it.
Your smoke is really...
So what?
Yu.
Well, since
You're leaving, what about the fish?
What about them?
They'll live or die on their own.
Ping. Ping.
Yeah.
Do me a favor later.
What is it?
Well, lend me that
Doggie's place or whatever,
Just for a while.
What for?
Why do you need Doggie's place?
Don't worry. It won't die.
No way.
Where's Doggie supposed to stay?
Doggie, he's trying to take your house from you.
Doggie, remember him.
He occupied your house.
What do you mean by occupy?
I told you, I'm borrowing it.
I didn't expect you to be so caring.
Are you kidding?
Lu Xixiao.
Where's my Doggie supposed to live?
Doggie...
Buy fish, get a free tank and some plants.
Where?
Go to Yu's place.
Go ask him.
-Yu's place? -Hurry.
[Today I am proud of Yangming, tomorrow Yangming will be proud of me]
I am wearing my uniform.
Why write my name down?
Your buttons aren't done up.
It's so hot.
-Buttoning up is hot. -Everyone's hot.
School ID badge.
Write faster.
I'm in a rush.
Lu Xixiao, Jiang Fan.
I know both your student IDs by heart.
Just let it go.
It's just too hot.
We're all classmates here.
Swimming pool tonight.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
What are you looking at? Give me back my badge.
Consider yourself lucky.
You guys...
It's a secret.
So many secrets.
What are you two whispering about?
And you were sneaking a smile.
None of your business.
What are you doing?
Looking at the future.
Looking at the future?
How?
Close your eyes.
Then you'll see it too.
I can't see anything.
So you're just messing with me.
What's the big deal
You wanted to talk about?
I wasn't trying
To snoop that day.
But I saw
That the book you're reading isn't high school level.
Honestly, I think
You need a study partner
More than self-teaching.
I'm the perfect fit.
So you just ran over here
To notify me?
You obviously don't want others to know
About you going abroad, right?
You could also go to
A tutoring center.
But you're studying by yourself.
I just want to earn some extra money.
Plus, I've got the time
And this place is convenient.
Most importantly,
I won't tell anyone.
What do you say?
I thought you were going to say
You're a great teacher.
I am a great teacher.
Pleasure working with you.
Take it or leave it.
Tomorrow, I'll make sure
The whole school knows
You're going abroad.
Don't you dare.
I'll give you two days to think about it.
[Yangming High School]
[Student Name: Feng Yue] [Student Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
[Student Name: Zhang Bingbing] [Student Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
[Student Name: Lu Xixiao] [Student Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
[Attendance Intention Survey: Unable to Attend]
Hello?
Hello.
Is this Ms. Guo Xiangling?
Yes.
Who is this?
I'm Lu Xixiao's English teacher
And vice homeroom teacher.
I noticed on the parent-teacher meeting form
[Unable to Attend]
That neither you nor his father
Will be attending. Is that right?
How come I've never heard him mention this?
How did you get my number?
Here's the thing.
Although he didn't fill in
Your number,
It's registered in the student
Emergency contact book.
Other parents also mention you often.
They said that you handled everything
Inside and out at home,
And contacting you would be right.
Then you've come to the right person.
Yes,
I take care of
All the household matters.
What's the matter?
Well,
The college entrance exam is coming up soon.
We still need you to attend
The parent-teacher meeting,
So we can discuss
His studies
And his application plans.
Okay.
Well, does
Xixiao know about this?
Kids his age
Tend to clash with their families.
[Student Name: Lu Xixiao] [Student Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
I'll get him to agree.
What?
I mean...
He's still the same lately,
Causing troubles.
I've talked to him.
Okay. So when is it?
The 25th of this month.
Okay, got it.
Alright.
I'll see you then.
Alright, see you then.
[Student Name: Lu Xixiao] [Student Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
We're expecting
A heatwave in the city over the next few days.
Citizens are reminded
To take fire precautions
And avoid prolonged exposure to the sun.
Experts from the traditional Chinese medicine hospital
Remind everyone
To stay calm
And not let the heat get to you.
With the college entrance exam approaching,
Students should be especially careful.
♪ Should I chase freedom all alone ♪
Watch out for heatstroke and physical discomfort.
With the extreme heat,
♪ Find an excuse, heed what I've known ♪
If you have elderly or children at home,
Remember to open the windows for fresh air.
♪ Every time I stop and stay ♪
Get down.
♪ For reasons that fade away ♪
Good morning!
Zhou Wan.
♪ Are you out there waiting for me ♪
Wan! Good morning.
Good morning.
You're on the bus too?
I was just on it too.
♪ Through the dark, bravely, steadily ♪
I wanted to find you,
But it was too crowded to get through.
Why aren't you wearing it?
♪ If I could run and land with you ♪
Just this once.
No way. Student ID.
It's you again, huh?
♪ After the long night ♪
Jiang Fan.
-Neither of them is wearing their uniform. -Grade 12.
-You only go after me? -Class 7.
♪ I'll find my way, no more lost inside ♪
Your ID number is 201307239, right?
♪ Thinking about ♪
Isn't this targeting me?
No.
♪ Fulfilling the last promise ♪
[No Regrets for Youth Sail Toward Your Dreams]
I'll trade you for a bun.
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
Morning, Shanshan.
Morning.
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
Run faster!
[College Entrance Exam Countdown]
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
[Youth Meets the Exam Now Is the Time to Strive]
[22 Days Until the Exam]
Wan.
♪ We've both held fragility ♪
♪ Talked through our misery ♪
♪ This time I'm holding tight to your will ♪
♪ Lighting up all the sparks ♪
♪ Hoping it doesn't slip away ♪
[Swimming Pool]
♪ In this boring universe ♪
♪ Drifting day by day ♪
♪ Until the day I choose to break away for you ♪
♪ And that's enough to do ♪
♪ Falling into your tenderness ♪
Lu Xixiao?
♪ Slowly being saved ♪
Okay.
I'll get going then.
Go ahead.
Why didn't you go
To class again today?
It's just evening self-study.
No one's waiting for me anyway.
Going there would just cause them trouble.
No.
Got something to repair?
You two know each other?
I never promised you anything.
If I beat you once,
You'll come to one class tomorrow.
Deal?
You're challenging him?
He holds the record
For this entire street.
I can come every day.
And I'm a fast learner.
Sooner or later, he'll lose to me.
She...
She said you'll lose to her.
What?
You don't dare?
She said you don't dare!
Just this once today.
If you lose, stop bothering me.
You're bothering him?
Oh boy. She's bothering you.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Don't put it there.
She's not coming back for evening study.
Give it to me.
Do you know where she went?
I don't know.
Hasn't she always been like this?
Sometimes when she finds the classroom too noisy,
She just finds a place to stay by herself.
Come here.
I have something to ask you.
Do you know
How she and Lu Xixiao
Met each other?
I haven't finished yet.
You don't know?
You live across from her
And you don't know?
Let me tell you,
She's been acting all mysterious lately.
I think
This guy Lu Xixiao
Is kind of dangerous.
I'm a little worried about her.
She never used to get involved
With people like that.
You don't know?
I said I know!
Why are you so fierce?
I won't thank you for your bread!
For you.
We'll play five rounds.
If she wins just one round,
He loses.
Game on.
Round one.
Ready? Go!
[Victory]
Round one. Lu Xixiao wins.
Round two.
Ready? Go!
Round two. Lu Xixiao wins.
Round three.
Round three. Lu Xixiao wins.
Round four.
Four laughs means four wins.
One last round left.
Round five.
It's the last round.
I know.
Don't go easy on me.
Because...
Yes!
I told you.
I'm a very fast learner.
See you tomorrow.
She's amazing.
She swapped the lightest parts
Based on the track map.
You didn't let her win, did you?
She volunteered to help you study.
Do you think she likes you?
If only her mind
Were that simple.
Are you going tomorrow?
I think you should go.
Hanging around here all day
Is so boring.
Go find her. It'll be fun.
I'm leaving.
Remember to lock the door.
Come down for breakfast.
I can't. I'm going to be late.
Then take some fruit to eat at school.
What about you? Did you take your meds today?
Not yet. I'll take it later.
No, I have to watch you take it,
Or you'll forget again.
Um...
Wan,
Have you been under
A lot of pressure lately?
I'm fine.
Why do you ask?
That photo.
Why are you thinking about Guo Yan?
I told you
Not to clean my room.
If something's on your mind,
Tell me.
Don't keep it all to yourself.
I've just been dreaming about her lately.
It's a bit annoying.
Why dream about her?
Without her, we still
Live our lives just fine.
The people who left
Have been gone.
Remember,
The most important thing right now
Is the exam.
You have to move forward.
Don't let anything stop you.
If you don't listen,
Don't blame me
For getting mad at you.
Don't be mad.
I'll listen.
You'll listen? Then have a bun.
Take your medicine first.
I will.
I have to watch you finish it
Before I can leave.
I'm taking it.
I'm leaving.
Don't choke.
I'm here.
You're on time this time.
You ran all the way here?
Thought I wouldn't be here?
Whether you show up or not,
I'll wait here until you do.
Seems like you really
Want to make this money.
It's not just for the money.
I'm very interested in you.
What, I can't be friends with you?
Just kidding.
Let's begin.
But it's true that I'll wait for you.
I prepared this for you.
500 phrases for speaking practice.
These are all high-scoring phrases.
You need to memorize them.
What are you looking at?
Why are you fidgeting so much?
Does it bother you?
No.
People who are good at spinning pens
Usually have fast brains.
But obviously, you're not.
Finished.
Stop it.
It's so annoying.
[English Test]
I feel like I don't
Really need you.
Your listening is okay.
Cloze and reading are not good.
Your foundation is too weak.
You still need to keep taking classes.
Why do you suddenly want to go abroad?
Would you be better prepared
If you had more time?
No reason.
I just don't want to be controlled by my family.
That's all.
I'll help you.
Just passing is enough.
Suit yourself.
So does that mean
You'll keep coming to class?
I guess.
You teach decently.
I don't want
To waste any more time.
Let's stick with this for now.
You look pretty decent too.
I said you teach decently.
Then let's plan on tutoring until
The parent-teacher meeting.
Will you come?
♪ If you had ever seen the fireflies ♪
♪ Inside my eyes ♪
Pleasure working with you.
♪ I think you would understand ♪
♪ Why I embrace the dark ♪
♪ People always want to reach out ♪
♪ But are afraid to pull their hands back ♪
♪ I choose to open my arms wide ♪
♪ And enjoy the weightlessness ♪
♪ If I could, I want to become ♪
♪ An astronomer ♪
♪ Lost in your night sky ♪
♪ Then fall and fall and fall ♪
[Without Passion, There Is No Hope]
♪ Maybe it's your gravity ♪
Don't just act like you're studying
[Give It Your All Today Win Your Future Tomorrow]
When the teacher's watching.
♪ That held me back from losing control ♪
You're not studying for the teacher,
But for yourselves.
Got it?
♪ When you passed by me by accident ♪
[Ride Your Dreams Conquer the Peak of the Exam]
Lu Xixiao.
Who's coming to the parent-teacher meeting from your family?
♪ I finally learned to fall ♪
Neither of them will probably come.
That won't do.
♪ Countless, unforgettable ♪
♪ No time left, so I ♪
[Ride Your Dreams Conquer the Peak of the Exam]
Wan! Zhou Wan!
♪ Can only fall toward you ♪
Hurry up, my stomach hurts!
♪ Too dazzling, too lonely, it's alright ♪
Hey, get a parent here, hear me?
♪ I believe in this encounter ♪
Half the cabinet fixed.
♪ Landing in the ruins of the galaxy ♪
♪ Exchanging our comets ♪
♪ Suddenly I am certain ♪
♪ This mud all over me ♪
♪ Is the proof of love ♪
I made this for you.
Mistake notebook.
Thanks.
I want a sausage, please!
A sausage, please!
Check, please!
See you tomorrow.
No idea.
You can just sleep.
You're really funny,
You're awesome. Let's go.
Mengmeng, class is over.
[Name: Lu Xixiao] [Class: Class 7, Grade 12]
Class is over!
Thank you.
Don't touch if you're not buying.
You might kill it.
[Fish Blessing Aquarium Shop]
I didn't touch it. It's almost dead anyway.
Is it dead?
Three days left.
Buy it now if you want it.
Weren't they kept
In a big fish tank before?
Why are they put
In separate bags now?
Isolating them?
Maybe they sell better this way.
Everything has its own fate.
The teacher asked me again recently
If you still take tutoring classes outside.
No.
I found another job.
What kind of job?
Tutoring someone again?
[Fish Blessing Aquarium Shop]
Tutoring him.
The game already started.
-Where did you go? -Hello.
How about you guys play another five rounds?
See you tonight.
Did he threaten you?
[Clearance Sale 3 Days Left]
He wouldn't do that.
He's actually quite nice.
And I approached him first.
You scared me.
I was held up on the way.
As for the missed lesson time,
I'll make up for it later.
Or I can give you a refund.
It's my responsibility.
It's fine. No big deal.
But it is my responsibility.
Where did you leave off?
What's in your bag?
Why is it leaking?
Leaking?
R-Right here.
I'm sorry.
Didn't he give you a box?
They were out of boxes.
Only bags were left.
When I went last time,
They still had boxes.
You've been there too?
Every time I pass by,
I feel terrible.
Yeah.
Things can't go on like this.
So what's the plan?
I just bought them all on impulse.
I haven't figured out a plan yet.
I'm afraid they'll suffocate soon.
I actually do have an idea.
I just don't know if you'd dare.
I will never forget this in my life.
Thank you for the tenderness you gave me.
This lab is broken
And hasn't been reported for repair.
It seems you know our school's
Chemistry lab
Inside and out.
You clearly never did cleaning duty.
You've clearly done plenty of bad things.
Who's there?
Why is the door open?
Is it broken?
Who's there?
-Run! -Who?
Let's go.
Who's there? I saw you!
Stop right there!
Stop right there! Don't run!
Little brats, where did you run off to?
Come here.
What are you doing?
It's a dead end ahead.
Stop!
Here.
Zhou Wan.
Take this.
No, no, no.
Zhou Wan.
Give me the beaker.
Get down quickly.
I can't.
-Get down. -I can't.
It's too high. I'm afraid of heights.
Don't be afraid. I'll catch you.
Come down.
Where did they go?
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
Don't run!
I saw you!
♪ A muted gray ♪
♪ Everything looks this way ♪
It's okay.
Come down. Don't worry.
♪ Another abandoned place ♪
Just one step away.
♪ Just forget the pain ♪
Got you.
♪ The fragments of our memories ♪
♪ Stolen, frozen ♪
Where'd they go?
Where do you think you're going?
♪ In this river ♪
♪ Lost inside a song ♪
Where'd they go?
♪ Far from where I belong ♪
Don't let me catch you!
♪ In this cold, bottomless hole ♪
♪ Something still remains ♪
♪ Hiding beneath the scars ♪
♪ I thought I'd shaken off your shadow ♪
♪ But it lingers on ♪
♪ Quiet as rain ♪
♪ Deep as sea ♪
[2026]
♪ It stirs and stirs and stirs ♪
♪ Forcing me to remember ♪
♪ Flickering like stars ♪
♪ Swaying like a flame ♪
♪ Hanging like a curse in midair ♪
♪ Burning like a wound ♪
♪ Quiet as rain ♪
♪ Deep as sea ♪
♪ It stirs and stirs and stirs ♪
♪ Forcing me to remember ♪
♪ Flickering like stars ♪
♪ Swaying like a flame ♪
♪ Hanging like a curse in midair ♪